<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- TODO: give a nice big rewrite to all o' these -->
    <string name="search_help">
		<![CDATA[
        <h3>Search basics</h3>
        <p>Derpibooru\'s search engine is based on the tags associated with the uploaded images. A
        search for <strong>pinkie pie</strong>, for example, yields the entries featuring Pinkie Pie.</p>
        <p>Separate multiple tags with a comma or <strong>&&</strong>. The queries are not case sensitive — the
        capitalization does not matter.</p>
        <p>You can mark the tags you do not want to appear with either <strong>!</strong> or <strong>-</strong>:<br>
        <strong>!fluttershy</strong> or <strong>-fluttershy</strong> matches pictures that do not feature Fluttershy.</p>
        <p>To request uploads that meet only a part of the criteria, use the disjunction (OR expression)
        specified with <strong>||</strong>, and separate the subexpressions with parentheses.</p>
        <p>Consider the following example: <strong>(twilight sparkle || fluttershy) && pinkie pie</strong> returns results that have
		either Twilight Sparkle or Fluttershy, and always Pinkie Pie.</p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="filters_help">
        <![CDATA[
        <h3>Content safety</h3>
        <p>The vast majority of content on Derpibooru (about 80%) is safe and suitable for all ages. By default, this is all you\'ll see on
        the site, and how most of our users browse. The default filters focus on art, so filter out things like memes and what some users
        would consider "spam".</p>
        <p>Filters let you customize what content you see on the site. This means that with the appropriate filter selected, you can access
        content which is not suitable for everyone, such as 18+ rated sexually explicit content, grimdark or gore.</p>
        <p><strong>By changing away from the default filters, you accept you are legally permitted to view this content in your jurisdiction.
        If in doubt, stick with the recommended default filters.</strong></p>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>